Okay so to center this platter onto this bat I'm going to use this pen tool here.
And I'm going to find a little spot on the base of the platter, and I'm going to hold this pen in it's own orbit around the edge of the platter.
So I'm going to turn my wheel, holding it in it's own spot.
I'm going to now start to center.
And you can see how I'm leaving a mark on one edge of the platter.
I'm going to find that mark and find my starting point and my end point over here.
I'm going to line my thumbs up or my fingers on these two spots and I'm simply going to push the plate forward, like that.
And I'm going to check it again.
Still a little bit off center, you can see this time our line is much larger, it goes all the way around to here.
Which means we're closer than we were before.
I'm going to line my fingers up again at either side, and push it forward slightly, like so.
And then check myself again.
Okay now you can see I'm pretty much moving around without leaving a gap in my circle.
There's a little bit of inconsistency in there, but basically this is now centered.
So the last thing we want to do, get a little bit of water on the bat so it sticks.
And just take some lumps of clay and simply secure the edges of the platter down.
Notice that I'm not sticking the clay to the actual platter, I'm sticking it to the bat and securing the edge.
We're going to do that in three spots around here.
And then the next portion of this exercise is going to be trimming this base and putting a foot on to it.
And we'll be doing that next.